Guide to the Washington State University Publications: Athletics Football Programs 1906-
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Washington State University Publications: Athletics Football Programs
1906-
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
WSU 031
8 linear feet of shelf space 16 containers
Football programs of Washington State University, also as Washington State College, dating from 1906 to present.
Intercollegiate football at Washington State University began with a November, 1894 game at the University of Idaho, and it has been played each season since (excepting the years 1943-1944, when it was canceled due to World War II).
The collection contains football programs from Washington State University (Washington State College before 1959). The 1906 program is the earliest known to exist, though we do not know for certain that there were no earlier ones. The collection is incomplete; the majority of the programs are home games.
The materials in this collection are organized chronologically by date of the game covered in the programs.
Many, but not all, of the football programs listed here can be found in their entirety in our digital collection of WSU football programs. The collection includes all MASC-held programs from 1906 to 1922, and all MASC-held home game programs from 1922 to 1980.
This collection is open and available for research use.
The “WSU Publications” collections are an accumulation of materials transferred to Washington State University Libraries’ Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections on a nearly daily basis. Some items are transferred directly by the University’s printing department. Many other materials have been forwarded by the Library’s serials cataloging unit. Other items come directly from university departments, and a significant number of publications have been donated by individuals. Most materials in it have no accession records.
MASC holds a large quantity of football materials, including but not limited to other series and items in this WSU Publications set (WSU 31), coaching films from many games (many of which are digitized and available online through the Washington State University Libraries YouTube channel), records of the Athletic Department and its heads, and university photographs collections. However, if you're looking for programs not listed here, we'd suggest that you contact either the WSU Athletic Department or the opposing team for the game you're looking for.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University. Department of Intercollegiate Athletics.; Washington State University--Football--History.
Football--Washington (State)--Pullman.
Colleges and Universities.; Sports and Recreation.
- Nov. 9, 1906 vs. Idaho. (Box 1)
- Oct. 18, 1912 vs. Idaho. (Box 1)
- Nov. 8, 1913 vs. Whitman. Homecoming. (Box 1)
- Nov. 7, 1914 vs. Idaho. Homecoming. (Box 1)
- Oct. 30, 1915 vs. Idaho. Idaho Homecoming. (Box 1)
- Nov. 6, 1915 vs. Montana. (Box 1)
- Jan. 1, 1916 vs. Brown. Rose Bowl. (Box 1)
- Nov. 25, 1916 vs. Gonzaga. (Box 1)
- Nov. 4, 1916 vs. Idaho. Homecoming. (Box 1)
- Oct. 14, 1916 vs. O.A.C. (Oregon State). (Box 1)
- Nov. 29, 1917 vs. Washington. Thanksgiving Day. (Box 1)
- Oct. 13, 1917 vs. Officers, 362nd Inf. (Box 1)
- Oct. 27, 1917 vs. Whitman. (Box 1)
- Nov. 3, 1917 vs. Idaho (and freshman vs. Lewiston HS). (Box 1)
- Oct. 25, 1919 vs. California. (Box 1)
- Nov. 1, 1919 vs. Idaho. (Box 1)
- Nov. 13, 1920 vs. O.A.C. (Oregon State). Homecoming. (Box 1)
- Oct. 30, 1920 vs. Montana. (Box 1)
- Nov. 5, 1921 vs. Oregon. (Box 1)
- Nov. 11, 1921 vs. O.A.C. (Oregon State). (Box 1)
- Oct. 21, 1921 vs. Idaho. (Box 1)
- Nov. 24, 1921 vs. Washington. Thanksgiving Day. (Box 1)
- Dec. 3, 1921 vs. USC. (Box 1)
- Nov. 10-11, 1922 vs. Oregon. 13th Annual Homecoming. (Box 1)
- Nov. 25, 1922 vs. O.A.C. (Oregon State). (Box 1)
- Nov. 30, 1922 vs. USC. Thanksgiving Day. (Box 1)
- Oct. 28, 1922 vs. Washington. Homecoming Day. (Box 1)
- Nov. 4, 1922 vs. California. (Box 1)
- Oct. 14, 1922 vs. Gonzaga. (Box 1)
- Nov. 24, 1923 vs. Washington. also program for UW vs Oregon, Dec 1. (Box 1)
- Oct. 27, 1923 vs. California. (Box 1)
- Nov. 3, 1923 vs. Oregon. Homecoming. (Box 1)
- Oct. 19, 1923 vs. Idaho. (Box 1)
- Oct. 11, 1924 vs. Gonzaga. (Box 1)
- Oct. 4, 1924 vs. Pacific University. (Box 1)
- Nov. 7, 1924 vs. OAC (Oregon State). Homecoming. (Box 1)
- Nov. 22, 1924 vs. Washington. (Box 1)
- Nov. 7, 1925 vs. California. (Box 1)
- Oct. 31, 1925 vs. Washington. Homecoming. (Box 1)
- Nov. 13, 1926 vs. Oregon. (Box 1)
- Oct. 15, 1927 vs. Gonzaga. (Box 1)
- Nov. 11, 1927 vs. Idaho. Homecoming. (Box 1)
- Oct. 8, 1927 vs. Montana. 2 copies. (Box 1)
- Oct. 29, 1927 vs. Oregon State. (Box 1)
- Oct. 8, 1927 vs. Montana. different copy. (Box 1)
- Oct. 20, 1928 vs. Oregon State. (Box 1)
- Nov. 29, 1928 vs. Washington. Thanksgiving Game. (Box 1)
- Oct. 13, 1928 vs. California. (Box 1)
- Oct. 12, 1929 vs. California. not in this collection, but one can be found in Cage 488, Eldon Jenne scrapbooks. (Box 1)
- Nov. 9, 1929 vs. Idaho. (Box 1)
- Nov. 30, 1929 vs. USC. (Box 1)
- Oct. 19, 1929 vs. Washington. Homecoming. (Box 1)
- Jan. 1, 1930 vs. Hawaii. New Year's Game. (Box 1)
- Oct. 4, 1930 vs. California. (Box 1)
- Oct. 11, 1930 vs. USC. Homecoming (USC). (Box 1)
- Oct. 25, 1930 vs. Montana. (Box 1)
- Nov. 15, 1930 vs. Washington. Homecoming Game. (Box 1)
- Nov. 8, 1930 vs. Idaho. Homecoming (Idaho?). (Box 1)
- Jan. 1, 1931 vs. Alabama. Rose Bowl. (Box 1)
- Tournament of Roses, New Year's Number of the Pasadena Post. (Box 1)
- Nov. 14, 1931 vs. Washington. (Box 2)
- Nov. 7, 1931 vs. Idaho. Dad's Day Game. (Box 2)
- Oct. 24, 1931 vs. Montana State. (Box 2)
- Oct. 17, 1931 vs. California. (Box 2)
- Oct. 3, 1931 vs. UCLA. Homecoming. (Box 2)
- Oct. 10, 1931 vs. USC. (Box 2)
- Dec. 5, 1931 vs. Tulane. (Box 2)
- Oct. 15, 1932 vs. California. (Box 2)
- Oct. 29, 1932 vs. Montana. (Box 2)
- Oct. 1, 1932 vs. USC. (Box 2)
- Nov. 5, 1932 vs. Idaho. Homecoming. (Box 2)
- Oct. 21, 1933 vs. California. Dad's Day Game. (Box 2)
- Oct. 7, 1933 vs. USC. (Box 2)
- Oct. 28, 1933 vs. Oregon State. (Box 2)
- Nov. 11, 1933 vs. Idaho. Armistice Day. (Box 2)
- Nov. 4, 1933 vs. Gonzaga. Gonzaga Homecoming. (Box 2)
- Nov. 25, 1933 vs. Washington. Homecoming. (Box 2)
- Sept. 29, 1934 vs. Montana. (Box 2)
- Nov. 10, 1934 vs. Idaho. Dad's Day Game. (Box 2)
- Oct. 27, 1934 vs. Oregon State. (Box 2)
- Oct. 13, 1934 vs. Gonzaga. Gonzaga Homecoming. (Box 2)
- Oct. 6, 1934 vs. USC. (Box 2)
- Nov. 2, 1934 vs. St. Mary's. (Box 2)
- Nov. 24, 1934 vs. Washington. (Box 2)
- Dec. 1, 1934 vs. University of Detroit. (Box 2)
- Sept. 28, 1935 vs. Puget Sound. (Box 2)
- Oct. 5, 1935 vs. Willamette. (Box 2)
- Oct. 19, 1935 vs. Washington. Homecoming. (Box 2)
- Nov. 9, 1935 vs. Idaho. (Box 2)
- Nov. 2, 1935 vs. Gonzaga. Dad's Day Game. (Box 2)
- Nov. 16, 1935 vs. USC. (Box 2)
- Nov. 30, 1935 vs. St. Mary's. (Box 2)
- Sept. 26, 1936 vs. Montana. (Box 2)
- Oct. 3, 1936 vs. Stanford. (Box 2)
- Oct. 10, 1936 vs. Idaho. (Box 2)
- Oct. 17, 1936 vs. USC. (Box 2)
- Oct. 24, 1936 vs. Oregon. (Box 2)
- Nov. 7, 1936 vs. Oregon State. (Box 2)
- Nov. 14, 1936 vs. UCLA. (Box 2)
- Nov. 26, 1936 vs. Washington. (Box 2)
- Sept. 25, 1937 vs. Gonzaga. (Box 2)
- Oct. 2, 1937 vs. Idaho. Dad's Day. (Box 2)
- Oct. 9, 1937 vs. California. (Box 2)
- Oct. 16, 1937 vs. Washington. Homecoming. (Box 2)
- Oct. 23, 1937 vs. UCLA. (Box 2)
- Oct. 30, 1937 vs. USC. (Box 2)
- Nov. 6, 1937 vs. Oregon. (Box 2)
- Nov. 20, 1937 vs. Oregon State. (Box 2)
- Sept. 24, 1938 vs. Oregon. (Box 2)
- Oct. 1, 1938 vs. California. (Box 2)
- Oct. 15, 1938 vs. USC. (Box 2)
- Oct. 22, 1938 vs. Oregon State. (Box 2)
- Oct. 29, 1938 vs. Gonzaga. (Box 2)
- Nov. 5, 1938 vs. UCLA. Homecoming, Dads' Day Game. (Box 2)
- Nov. 12, 1938 vs. Idaho. Idaho Homecoming. (Box 2)
- Nov. 26, 1938 vs. Washington. (Box 2)
- Dec. 3, 1938 vs. Oklahoma. (Box 2)
- Sept. 23, 1939 vs. Gonzaga. (Box 3)
- Oct. 14, 1939 vs. Washington. Homecoming. (Box 3)
- Oct. 28, 1939 vs. Oregon State. (Box 3)
- Nov. 4, 1939 vs. Oregon. (Box 3)
- Nov. 11, 1939 vs. Idaho. Homecoming, Armistice Day. (Box 3)
- Nov. 30, 1939 vs. UCLA. (Box 3)
- Sept. 28, 1940 vs. USC. (Box 3)
- Oct. 5, 1940 vs. Montana. (Box 3)
- Oct.12, 1940 vs. California. (Box 3)
- Oct. 19, 1940 vs. Stanford. Homecoming Day. (Box 3)
- Oct. 26, 1940 vs. Oregon. Dads' Day Game. (Box 3)
- Nov. 2, 1940 vs. Idaho. Idaho Homecoming. (Box 3)
- Nov. 9, 1940 vs. Oregon State. (Box 3)
- Nov. 16, 1940 vs. UCLA. (Box 3)
- Nov. 23, 1940 vs. Gonzaga. (Box 3)
- Nov. 30, 1940 vs. Washington. (Box 3)
- Sept. 26, 1941 vs. UCLA. (Box 3)
- Oct. 4, 1941 vs. California. (Box 3)
- Oct. 11, 1941 vs. Washington. (Box 3)
- Oct. 25, 1941 vs. Oregon State. Dad's Day. (Box 3)
- Nov. 1, 1941 vs. Oregon. (Box 3)
- Nov. 8, 1941 vs. Idaho. (Box 3)
- Nov. 15, 1941 vs. Stanford. (Box 3)
- Nov. 22, 1941 vs. Gonzaga. (Box 3)
- Dec. 6, 1941 vs. Texas A&M. (Box 3)
- Sept. 26, 1942 vs. Stanford. (Box 3)
- Oct. 3, 1942 vs. Oregon. Homecoming. (Box 3)
- Oct. 10, 1942 vs. Montana. (Box 3)
- Oct. 17, 1942 vs. USC. (Box 3)
- Oct. 24, 1942 vs. Oregon State. (Box 3)
- Nov. 7, 1942 vs. Michigan State. (Box 3)
- Nov. 14, 1942 vs. Idaho. (Box 3)
- Nov. 21, 1942 vs. Second Air Force. (Box 3)
- Nov. 28, 1942 vs. Washington. (Box 3)
- 1943-1944: No Football Played At Washington State College due to WWII. (Box 3)
- Sept. 29, 1945 vs. Idaho. (Box 3)
- Oct. 6, 1945 vs. Oregon State. (Box 3)
- Oct. 13, 1945 vs. Washington. (Box 3)
- Oct. 20, 1945 vs. Oregon. (Box 3)
- Oct. 27, 1945 vs. Idaho. (Box 3)
- Nov. 3, 1945 vs. California. (Box 3)
- Nov. 10, 1945 vs. Oregon. Dad's Day. (Box 3)
- Nov. 17, 1945 vs. Oregon State. (Box 3)
- Nov. 24, 1945 vs. Washington. Homecoming (two different copies). (Box 3)
- Sept. 27, 1946 vs. USC. (Box 3)
- Oct. 5, 1946 vs. Idaho. (Box 3)
- Oct. 12, 1946 vs. Washington. Homecoming. (Box 3)
- Oct. 19, 1946 vs. Oregon. (Box 3)
- Oct. 26, 1946 vs. Oregon State. (Box 3)
- Nov. 2, 1946 vs. California. (Box 3)
- Nov. 9, 1946 WSU JV vs. UW JV. 2 different front covers. (Box 3)
- Nov. 30, 1946 vs. Michigan State. (Box 3)
- Sept. 30, 1947 vs. Penn. State. (Box 3)
- Sept. 27, 1947 vs. USC. 2 different front covers. (Box 3)
- Oct. 11, 1947 vs. Michigan State. (Box 3)
- Oct. 18, 1947 vs. California. (Box 3)
- Oct. 25, 1947 vs. Montana. Dad's Day Game. (Box 3)
- Oct. 31, 1947 vs. University of Portland. (Box 3)
- Nov. 8, 1947 vs. Oregon. Homecoming. (Box 3)
- Nov. 15, 1947 vs. Oregon State. (Box 3)
- Nov. 22, 1947 vs. Washington. (Box 3)
- Oct. 2, 1948 vs. Stanford. (Box 4)
- Oct. 16, 1948 vs. Washington. Homecoming. (Box 4)
- Oct. 30, 1948 vs. Idaho. (Box 4)
- Nov. 6, 1948 vs. Oregon State. Dad's Day Game. (Box 4)
- Nov. 20, 1948 vs. Michigan State. (Box 4)
- Nov. 27, 1948 vs. Penn. State. (Box 4)
- Sept. 17, 1949 vs. Utah State. Spokane Day. (Box 4)
- Sept. 24, 1949 vs. Montana. (Box 4)
- Oct. 1, 1949 vs. USC. (Box 4)
- Oct. 8, 1949 vs. Oregon. Dad's Day. (Box 4)
- Oct. 22, 1949 vs. UCLA. (Box 4)
- Nov. 5, 1949 vs. California. (Box 4)
- Nov. 19, 1949 vs. Washington. (Box 4)
- Sept. 23, 1950 vs. Utah State. (Box 4)
- Sept. 30, 1950 vs. UCLA. (Box 4)
- Oct. 7, 1950 vs. USC. (Box 4)
- Oct. 14, 1950 vs. Montana. Dad's Day. (Box 4)
- Oct. 28, 1950 vs. Idaho. (Box 4)
- Nov. 18, 1950 vs. Oregon State. Homecoming. (Box 4)
- Nov. 25, 1950 vs. Washington. Dedication Day. (Box 4)
- Sept. 22, 1951 vs. USC. (Box 4)
- Sept. 29, 1951 vs. Santa Clara University. (Box 4)
- Oct. 5, 1951 vs. Oklahoma A&M. (Box 4)
- Oct. 13, 1951 vs. California. (Box 4)
- Oct. 27, 1951 vs. Oregon. Homecoming. (Box 4)
- Nov. 3, 1951 vs. Stanford. (Box 4)
- Nov. 10, 1951 vs. Idaho. Homecoming (Idaho). (Box 4)
- Nov. 17, 1951 vs. Montana. (Box 4)
- Nov. 24, 1951 vs. Washington. (Box 4)
- Sept. 19, 1952 vs. USC. (Box 4)
- Sept. 27, 1952 vs. Stanford. Dad's Day. (Box 4)
- Oct. 18, 1952 vs. Ohio State. (Box 4)
- Oct. 25, 1952 vs. Oregon State. Homecoming. (Box 4)
- Nov. 1, 1952 vs. Idaho. (Box 4)
- Nov. 8, 1952 vs. Oregon. Homecoming. (Box 4)
- Nov. 15, 1952 vs. California. (Box 4)
- Nov. 29, 1952 vs. Washington. (Box 4)
- Sept. 19, 1953 vs. USC. (Box 4)
- Sept. 26, 1953 vs. College of the Pacific. (Box 4)
- Oct. 3, 1953 vs. Iowa. (Box 4)
- Oct. 10, 1953 vs. Oregon. Homecoming and Dad's Day. (Box 4)
- Oct. 17, 1953 vs. Idaho. (Box 4)
- Oct. 24, 1953 vs. UCLA. (Box 4)
- Oct. 31, 1953 vs. Stanford. (Box 4)
- Nov. 7, 1953 vs. Texas Christian University. (Box 4)
- Nov. 14, 1953 vs. Oregon State. Homecoming and Stadium Dedication (Oregon). (Box 4)
- Nov. 21, 1953 vs. Washington. (Box 4)
- Sept. 17, 1954 vs. USC. (Box 4)
- Oct. 9, 1954 vs. Oregon State. Homecoming. (Box 4)
- Oct. 23, 1954 vs. Idaho. Dad's Day. (Box 4)
- Oct. 30, 1954 vs. Stanford. (Box 4)
- Nov. 20, 1954 vs. Washington. (Box 4)
- Sept. 17, 1955 vs. USC. (Box 4)
- Oct. 1, 1955 vs. UCLA. Dad's Day. (Box 4)
- Oct. 8, 1955 vs. California. (Box 4)
- Nov. 5, 1955 vs. Oregon. Homecoming. (Box 4)
- Nov. 12, 1955 vs. San Jose State College. (Box 4)
- Nov. 19, 1955 vs. Washington. (Box 4)
- Sept. 22, 1956 vs. Stanford. 2 differenent covers. (Box 4)
- Oct. 6, 1956 vs. Idaho. (Box 4)
- Oct. 20, 1956 vs. Oregon State. (Box 4)
- Oct. 27, 1956 vs. College of the Pacific. (Box 4)
- Nov. 3, 1956 vs. USC. (Box 4)
- Nov. 10, 1956 vs. Oregon. (Box 4)
- Nov. 17, 1956 vs. California. (Box 4)
- Nov. 24, 1956 vs. Washington. (Box 4)
- Sept. 21, 1957 vs. Nebraska. (Box 4)
- Sept. 28, 1957 vs. California. (Box 4)
- Oct. 5, 1957 vs. Iowa. (Box 4)
- Oct. 12, 1957 vs. Stanford. (Box 4)
- Oct. 19, 1957 vs. Oregon. Homecoming. (Box 4)
- Oct. 26, 1957 vs. USC. (Box 4)
- Nov. 2, 1957 vs. Oregon State. Homecoming (Oregon). (Box 4)
- Nov. 9, 1957 vs. UCLA. (Box 4)
- Nov. 16, 1957 vs. Idaho. Dad's day. (Box 4)
- Nov. 23, 1957 vs. Washington. (Box 4)
- Sept. 20, 1958 vs. Stanford. (Box 5)
- Sept. 27, 1958 vs. Northwestern. (Box 5)
- Oct. 4, 1958 vs. California. (Box 5)
- Oct. 18, 1958 vs. Oregon. (Box 5)
- Oct. 25, 1958 vs. USC. (Box 5)
- Nov. 1, 1958 vs. UCLA. (Box 5)
- Nov. 8, 1958 vs. Oregon State. Homecoming. (Box 5)
- Nov. 15, 1958 vs. College of the Pacific. (Box 5)
- Nov. 22, 1958 vs. Washington. (Box 5)
- Sept. 19, 1959 vs. California. (Box 5)
- Sept. 26, 1959 vs. San Jose State. (Box 5)
- Oct. 17, 1959 vs. Stanford. (Box 5)
- Oct. 24, 1959 vs. Idaho. (Box 5)
- Oct. 31, 1959 vs. Oregon State. (Box 5)
- Nov. 14, 1959 vs. Oregon. (Box 5)
- Nov. 21, 1959 vs. Washington. (Box 5)
- Nov. 26, 1959 vs. Houston. (Box 5)
- Sept. 17, 1960 vs. Stanford. (Box 5)
- Sept. 23, 1960 vs. Denver University. (Box 5)
- Oct. 1, 1960 vs. Arizona State. (Box 5)
- Oct. 8, 1960 vs. California. (Box 5)
- Oct. 22, 1960 vs. College of the Pacific. Dad's Day and Band Day. (Box 5)
- Oct. 29, 1960 vs. San Jose State. (Box 5)
- Nov. 5, 1960 vs. Oregon State. Homecoming. (Box 5)
- Nov. 19, 1960 vs. Washington. (Box 5)
- Sept. 23, 1961 vs. Missouri. (Box 5)
- Sept. 30, 1961 vs. Utah State. (Box 5)
- Oct. 7, 1961 vs. Texas. (Box 5)
- Oct. 14, 1961 vs. Idaho. (Box 5)
- Oct. 21, 1961 vs. Indiana. (Box 5)
- Oct. 28, 1961 vs. San Jose State. (Box 5)
- Nov. 10, 1961. WSU Coubabes vs. Idaho Frosh. (Box 5)
- Nov. 11, 1961 vs. Oregon. Homecoming. (Box 5)
- Nov. 18, 1961 vs. Stanford. (Box 5)
- Nov. 25, 1961 vs. Washington. (Box 5)
- Sept. 22, 1962 vs. San Jose State. Band Day. (Box 5)
- Sept. 29, 1962 vs. Wyoming. (Box 5)
- Oct. 6, 1962 vs. Arizona State. (Box 5)
- Oct. 13, 1962 vs. Stanford. (Box 5)
- Oct. 20, 1962 vs. Indiana. (Box 5)
- Oct. 27, 1962 vs. Pacific. (Box 5)
- Nov. 3, 1962 vs. Oregon State. Homecoming. (Box 5)
- Nov. 9, 1962 WSU Coubabes vs. Idaho Frosh. 2 different covers. (Box 5)
- Nov. 10, 1962 vs. Oregon. Oregon Homecoming. (Box 5)
- Nov. 18, 1962 vs. Idaho. (Box 5)
- Nov. 24, 1962 vs. Washington. (Box 5)
- Sept. 28, 1963 vs. Iowa. (Box 5)
- Oct. 5, 1963 vs. Arizona State. (Box 5)
- Oct. 12, 1963 vs. San Jose State. Dad's Day and Band Day. (Box 5)
- Nov. 2, 1963 vs. Idaho. (Box 5)
- Nov. 9, 1963 vs. Oregon. Homecoming. (Box 5)
- Nov. 16, 1963 vs. Stanford. (Box 5)
- Sept. 19, 1964 vs. Stanford. (Box 5)
- Sept. 26, 1964 vs. Wyoming. (Box 5)
- Oct. 10, 1964 vs. Pacific. (Box 5)
- Oct. 24, 1964 vs. Idaho. (Box 5)
- Oct. 31, 1964 vs. Oregon State. (Box 5)
- Nov. 21, 1964 vs. Washington. (Box 5)
- Oct. 9, 1965 vs. Villanova. (Box 6)
- Oct. 16, 1965 vs. Arizona. (Box 6)
- Nov. 6, 1965 vs. Oregon. (Box 6)
- Nov. 13, 1965 vs. Arizona State. (Box 6)
- Nov. 20, 1965 vs. Washington. (Box 6)
- Sept. 17, 1966 vs. California. (Box 6)
- Sept. 23, 1966 vs. Houston. (Box 6)
- Oct. 1, 1966 vs. Baylor. (Box 6)
- Oct. 8, 1966 vs. Arizona State. (Box 6)
- Oct. 22, 1966 vs. Idaho. (Box 6)
- Oct. 29, 1966 vs. Oregon State. (Box 6)
- Nov. 12, 1966 vs. Arizona. (Box 6)
- Nov. 19, 1966 vs. Washington. (Box 6)
- Sept. 15, 1967 vs. USC. (Box 6)
- Sept. 30, 1967 vs. UCLA. (Box 6)
- Oct. 7, 1967 vs. Baylor. (Box 6)
- Oct. 14, 1967 vs. Stanford. (Box 6)
- Oct. 21, 1967 vs. Arizona State. (Box 6)
- Oct. 28, 1967 vs. Oregon State. Oregon State Homecoming. (Box 6)
- Nov. 11, 1967 vs. Idaho. (Box 6)
- Nov. 25, 1967 vs. Washington. (Box 6)
- May 17, 1968. WSU Alumni vs. Varsity. (Box 6)
- Sept. 21, 1968 vs. Idaho. (Box 6)
- Oct. 5, 1968 vs. Utah. (Box 6)
- Oct. 12, 1968 vs. Arizona State. (Box 6)
- Oct. 19, 1968 vs. Stanford. Band Day. (Box 6)
- Oct. 26, 1968 vs. Oregon State. Homecoming. (Box 6)
- Nov. 16, 1968 vs. San Jose State. (Box 6)
- Nov. 23, 1968 vs. Washington. (Box 6)
- Nov. 1, 1969 vs. Pacific. Homecoming. (Box 6)
- Oct. 4, 1969 vs. Oregon. (Box 6)
- Sept. 19, 1970 vs. Idaho. (Box 6)
- Oct. 17, 1970 vs. Stanford. (Box 6)
- Nov. 7, 1970 vs. USC. (Box 6)
- Nov. 14, 1970 vs. Oregon State. Homecoming. (Box 6)
- Nov. 21, 1970 vs. Washington. (Box 6)
- Sept. 18, 1971 vs. Arizona. (Box 6)
- Oct. 9, 1971 vs. UCLA. Dad's Day, Band Day. (Box 6)
- Oct. 23, 1971 vs. Stanford. (Box 6)
- Oct. 30, 1971 vs. Oregon. Homecoming. (Box 6)
- Nov. 13, 1971 vs. Oregon State. (Box 6)
- Sept. 9, 1972 vs. Kansas. (Box 6)
- Sept. 16, 1972 vs. California. (Box 6)
- Sept. 23, 1972 vs. Arizona. (Box 6)
- Sept. 30, 1972 vs. Utah. (Box 6)
- Oct. 14, 1972 vs. Oregon. Oregon Homecoming. (Box 6)
- Oct. 21, 1972 vs. Oregon State. (Box 6)
- Oct. 28, 1972 vs. UCLA. (Box 6)
- Nov. 4, 1972 vs. USC. Cougar Day. (Box 6)
- Nov. 11, 1972 vs. Stanford. Dad's Day. (Box 6)
- Nov. 12, 1972. WSU JV vs. UW JV (Evergreen bowl). (Box 6)
- Nov. 18, 1972 vs. Washington. (Box 6)
- Sept. 15, 1973 vs. Kansas. (Box 7)
- Sept. 29, 1973 vs. Idaho. 2 copies, one inside Touchdown Illustrated Mag. (Box 7)
- Nov. 10, 1973 vs. Oregon State. inside Touchdown Illustrated Mag. (Box 7)
- Sept. 14, 1974 vs. Kansas. (Box 7)
- Oct. 5, 1974 vs. Ohio State. (Box 7)
- Oct. 12, 1974 vs. USC. (Box 7)
- Oct. 19, 1974 vs. UCLA. (Box 7)
- Oct. 26, 1974 vs. Stanford. (Box 7)
- Nov. 9, 1974 vs. Oregon State. (Box 7)
- Sept. 13, 1975 vs. Kansas. (Box 7)
- Sept. 20, 1975 vs. Utah. (Box 7)
- Sept. 27, 1975 vs. California. (Box 7)
- Oct. 4, 1975 vs. Illinois. Ill. Dad's Day. (Box 7)
- Oct. 11, 1975 vs. USC. (Box 7)
- Oct. 25, 1975 vs. Stanford. (Box 7)
- Nov. 1, 1975 vs. Oregon. (Box 7)
- Nov. 8, 1975 vs. Oregon State. (Box 7)
- Nov. 15, 1975 vs. Idaho. (Box 7)
- Oct. 9, 1976 vs. USC. (Box 7)
- Oct. 16, 1976 vs. UCLA. (Box 7)
- Oct. 23, 1976 vs. Stanford. (Box 7)
- Oct. 30, 1976 vs. Oregon. 2 copies with different covers. (Box 7)
- Nov. 6, 1976 vs. Oregon State. (Box 7)
- Nov. 13, 1976 vs. California. (Box 7)
- Nov. 20, 1976 vs. Washington. (Box 7)
- Oct. 8, 1977 vs. California. (Box 7)
- Oct. 15, 1977 vs. UCLA. (Box 7)
- Oct. 29, 1977 vs. Oregon. (Box 7)
- Nov. 12, 1977 vs. Idaho. (Box 7)
- Sept. 9, 1978 vs. UNLV. Cougar Kick Off. (Box 8)
- Sept. 16, 1978 vs. Idaho. Band Day. (Box 8)
- Sept. 23, 1978 vs. Arizona State. Pac-10 Kick Off. (Box 8)
- Sept. 30, 1978 vs. Army. (Box 8)
- Oct. 21, 1978 vs. Stanford. Homecoming. (Box 8)
- Nov. 4, 1978 vs. Oregon State. Dad's Weekend. (Box 8)
- Nov. 25, 1978 vs. Washington. Apple Bowl. (Box 8)
- Sept. 8, 1979 vs. Arizona. Pac-10 Opener. (Box 8)
- Oct. 13, 1979 vs. UCLA. Homecoming. (Box 8)
- Nov. 10, 1979 vs. California. Dad's Day. (Box 8)
- Sept. 13, 1980 vs. San Jose State. (Box 8)
- Sept. 27, 1980 vs. Army. (Box 8)
- Oct. 4, 1980 vs. Pacific. Cougar Club and Band Day. (Box 8)
- Oct. 25, 1980 vs. Stanford. Dads' Day. (Box 8)
- Nov. 8, 1980 vs. Oregon State. Homecoming. (Box 8)
- Nov. 22, 1980 vs. Washington. (Box 8)
- Sept. 12, 1981 vs. Montana State. Montana Days. (Box 8)
- Sept. 26, 1981 vs. Arizona State. Land Alive Day. (Box 8)
- Oct. 3, 1981 vs. Pacific. Young America Day. (Box 8)
- Oct. 17, 1981 vs. UCLA. Homecoming. (Box 8)
- Nov. 7, 1981 vs. Oregon. Dads' Day. (Box 8)
- Nov. 14, 1981 vs. California. Spokane Centennial. (Box 8)
- Dec. 18, 1981 vs. Brigham Young. Holiday Bowl IV. (Box 8)
- Sept. 11, 1982 vs. Idaho. Battle of the Palouse. (Box 8)
- Sept. 18, 1982 vs. Colorado. Cougar Mania, National Gray W Day. (Box 8)
- Sept. 25, 1982 vs. Minnesota. (Box 8)
- Oct. 2, 1982 vs. Tennessee. (Box 8)
- Oct. 9, 1982 vs. Oregon State. Land Grant Days. (Box 8)
- Oct. 23, 1982 vs. Stanford. (Box 8)
- Sept. 3, 1983 vs. Montana State. Montana Days. (Box 9)
- Sept. 10, 1983 vs. Michigan. (Box 9)
- Sept. 17, 1983 vs. Arizona. Land Grant, Cougar Mania. (Box 9)
- Sept. 24, 1983 vs. Nevada-Las Vegas. Band Youth Day. (Box 9)
- Oct. 8, 1983 vs. USC. (Box 9)
- Oct. 15, 1983 vs. UCLA. Homecoming. (Box 9)
- Oct. 29, 1983 vs. Oregon. Dads' Day. (Box 9)
- Nov. 12, 1983 vs. California. National Gray "W" Day. (Box 9)
- Sept. 22, 1984 vs. Ball State. Band Day. (Box 9)
- Oct. 6, 1984 vs. USC. Homecoming. (Box 9)
- Oct. 13, 1984 vs. UCLA. (Box 9)
- Oct. 20, 1984 vs. Stanford. (Box 9)
- Nov. 3, 1984 vs. Oregon State. Land Grant, Parents' Day. (Box 9)
- Nov. 17, 1984 vs. Washington. Gray "W," Hall of Fame. (Box 9)
- Aug. 31, 1985 vs. Oregon. Gray "W" Day. (Box 9)
- Sept. 21, 1985 vs. Utah. (Box 9)
- Oct. 12, 1985 vs. Oregon State. Band Day. (Box 9)
- Oct. 19, 1985 vs. UCLA. Homecoming. (Box 9)
- Oct. 26, 1985 vs. Arizona State. Land Grant Wheat Bowl. (Box 9)
- Nov. 2, 1985 vs. USC. (Box 9)
- Nov. 16, 1985 vs. Montana State. Youth Day. (Box 9)
- Nov. 23, 1985 vs. Washington. Apple Cup. (Box 9)
- Sept. 6, 1986 vs. UNLV. Armed Forces Day. (Box 10)
- Sept. 13, 1986 vs. San Jose State. Band/Youth Day. (Box 10)
- Sept. 20, 1986 at California. (Box 10)
- Oct. 4, 1986 vs. Oregon State. Dads' Day. (Box 10)
- Nov. 8, 1986 vs. Arizona. Land Grant Day / Wheat Bowl. (Box 10)
- Nov. 22, 1986 vs. Washington. (Box 10)
- No 1987 programs. (Box 10)
- Sept. 3, 1988 vs. Illinois. (Box 10)
- Sept. 17, 1988 vs. Oregon. (Box 10)
- Oct. 8, 1988 vs. California. Homecoming. (Box 10)
- Oct. 22, 1988 vs. Arizona State. Dads' Day. (Box 10)
- Nov. 12, 1988 vs. Oregon State. Land Grant Day. (Box 10)
- Nov. 19, 1988 vs. Washington. (Box 10)
- Dec. 25, 1988 vs. Houston. Eagle Aloha Bowl. (Box 10)
- 1989 Football Facts (statistics and schedule for 1989). (Box 10)
- Sept. 2, 1989 vs. Idaho. Centennial / Hall of Fame Day. (Box 10)
- Sept. 7, 1989 at BYU. (Box 10)
- Sept. 16, 1989 vs. Oregon State. Band Day. (Box 10)
- Oct. 14, 1989 vs. Stanford. Land Grant Day. (Box 10)
- Oct. 21, 1989 vs. Arizona. Homecoming. (Box 10)
- Nov. 11, 1989 at California. (Box 10)
- Sept. 8, 1990 vs. Wyoming. Band Day, Future Cougar Day, Armed Forces Day. (Box 10)
- Sept. 22, 1990 vs. California. Dads' Day. (Box 10)
- Sept. 14, 1991 vs. Fresno State. Band Day, Future Cougar Day, Armed Forces Day. (Box 10)
- Oct. 5, 1991 vs. Oregon State. Homecoming/Shrine Game. (Box 10)
- Nov. 9, 1991 vs. Arizona. Dads' Day. (Box 10)
- Nov. 16, 1991 vs. Stanford. Land Grant Day. (Box 10)
- Sept. 5, 1992 vs. Montana. (Box 11)